fleetmon.com 2012-11-07

# FleetMon - ship and port database with AIS live position maps for vessel tracking - FleetMon.com

Your privacy is of paramount importance to Fleetmon.com. This policy applies to all products and services offered by Fleetmon.com.

Information we gather from you:

  * Because the Fleetmon.com Service houses your website statistics on our servers, you must register for a Fleetmon.com account. The registration process asks for a username, password, email address and some personally identifiable information including name, address and contact details.
  * When you log into the Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * When you send email or other communication to Fleetmon.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

Fleetmon.com will not share your personal information without your consent or unless required by law.

By the nature of our Service, Fleetmon.com will gather statistics about the usage of your website and store that information. Fleetmon.com will not share your website statistics without your consent.

Fleetmon.com only processes personal information for the purpose of providing, improving, ensuring the delivery of, and developing new services to users.

If Fleetmon.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information such as the number of sites using Fleetmon.com, for example. Such information does not identify you individually.

We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop, or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

This Privacy Policy applies to websites and services that are owned and operated by Fleetmon.com. We do not exercise control over the sites that may be linked from our website. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

Fleetmon.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time and at Fleetmon.com's sole discretion. However, your rights will not be reduced without your explicit consent.
